念能力は 次の６つの系統に分類される
Given his personality, he's probably already warmed
to these opponents...
あらゆるものが持つ 本来の働きや力を強化する能力
I doubt he'd sell me out, but it's probable that he'll accidentally
say something he shouldn't.
発したオーラを 別の性質に変えてしまう能力
My chance will come after they leave. I will defeat them...
ミトさん 俺　必ず　ジンを見つけるから！
He, too, is one of Morel's students. This won't work.
ジンに会ったら また　島に戻って来るからね！
In our current condition,
we don't stand a chance...
それまで元気でね！
I'm pretty sure that Knuckle's using
less than half of his strength.
ゴンとキルアが くじら島を旅立った頃
I don't sense anyone else around. It's the perfect chance.
クラピカも　また 新たな旅立ちの時を迎えていた
When I take my target down, I am
always deliberate and thorough.
私を覚えているのか？
That's what it takes to be a UMA Hunter.
自力で　この斡旋所を 見つけたくらいだから
What's wrong? It's the perfect opportunity.
頭が切れることは認めるよ。
Right now, I can easily...
だけど　大切なお客に　あんたを 紹介するわけにはいかないねぇ。 経験不足とか 言うつもりはないわ。
Go...
ひよっこでもいいっていう客は いるし
Go!
何だと？
Shoot McMahon...
何も見えないでしょ？
He is a coward.
見えるようになったら もういっぺん　おいでよ。
Hey, Killua... Why wasn't Knuckle-san good enough?
見えてなくとも 感じ取るくらいは　できるんだな。
His approach isn't in line
with this mission's objective. He's too soft. And he gets attached to animals too easily.
何のまねだ!? これか？ まぁ　ちょっとした　お遊び。
And he did end up volunteering
to help us, somehow...
ひよっこ後輩への 先輩からのご指導ってところか。
Yeah...
あっ！ こいつを　すり取ったどころか
They can maintain their Ren for two hours
without having to really concentrate.
街で俺と　すれ違ったことすら 気づかなかったろ。
That's a good sign...
貴様！ 私のハンターライセンスを返せ！
If they can do it for three hours, I might consider letting them fight
Knuckle when they're fully rested.
「念」も知らない見習に 俺が倒せるかな？
Knuckle will then be forced
to use his full strength.
「ネン」？
I hope it will be enough to teach them...
フッ。 試してみるかい？
That which they lack, that which they need. But that still only takes them halfway.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
And that means they'll have no more
than a day left before time's up...
分かったか？ お前には　まだ足りねえんだよ。
I'm not sure they can make it.
今日は お前が　どの系統に属するか
I should probably prepare for my escape...
調べてみよう。
Save my own skin.
水の中に不純物か。
From what I've seen, you're only two-thirds through your training to become strong enough
具現化系だな　お前は。
to force Knuckle into using his full strength...
具現化系…。
Uh-oh...
オーラを物質化するのが 得意なタイプだな。
She knows exactly what's going on.
そうか 強化系が理想だったのだが…。
Huh? Is that true, Bisky?
こればっかりは 生まれ持ったもんだからな。
But it'll be fine!
強化系の技も 覚えられないわけじゃないがな。
We'll definitely beat him before the deadline!
今日は　そこんとこ 少し詳しく話しておこうか。
How can you be so sure?! The situation hasn't improved at all...
具現化系の能力を １００％習得できる才能が お前にあるとしよう。
You said it was all right for
me to speak up, so I will.
すると　他の能力の習得率は こうなる。
You have no chance to defeat Knuckle! They didn't give you enough time...
自分の系統でない能力を
Lately, I find myself gripping a kitchen knife, staring at it to calm myself.
完璧に覚えることはできない。 自分の系統から遠い能力ほど 習得率は下がる。 特質系がゼロなのは？
That means I'm nearly over the edge, so if you run at once, before it's too late,
I probably won't try to chase and kill you.
特質系ってのは特別でな
If not for her outbursts...
覚えようと思って 覚えられるもんじゃねえんだ。
This would be a pleasant meal...
大抵が血統だったり
We aren't gonna run away.
特殊な環境で育ったりが作用する 個性的な能力だからな。
How many times do I have to say it? What else can you do?
なぜ この位置にあるかっていうと
As you currently are, you cannot defeat Knuckle!
後天的に 特質系に変わる確率が高いのが
We'll win! Pinky swear.
両隣の 具現化系と操作系だからだ。
Come on... Hurry up!
そういう意味では　お前は まだ可能性があるほうだな。 以前　お前は言ってたな。
I pinky swear that we'll beat Knuckle
and Shoot before the deadline.
)
If I break my promise, I have to
swallow a thousand needles...
((私は…
Pinky sworn!
私には… １人で戦い抜ける力が　いる！))
On the island I'm from, there's another part. You go like this and put your thumbs together.
そのためには 強化系能力の習得が
Okay, now it's a promise. By the way, Palm-san,
what did you use to flavor this?
最優先だという　お前の考えは 正論だ。
Oh... Ah, it's broth from chicken bones...
攻め　守り　癒やしを 一番効率よく補強できるのが 強化系だからな。
Gon's getting really good at handling Palm.
だが　具現化系のお前では 強化系の技　威力ともに 半分程度しか習得できない。
I suspect she's the one leading
things in that direction...
能力以上の力を使えば 必ず　どこかに　ひずみが生じる。
I let a Kunai chicken cook overnight, then I let it sit for another night.
それは弱点となり 致命傷になりかねない。
Ten days left. Don't say that like a countdown to our death!
うん… ひと言で言うと難しいな。
This is it...
攻撃力　防御力ともに高い 強化系に対し 具現化系は　能力のバランスが 悪い場合が多い。
Smoke that covers the forest like fog. Baital squad here.
その代わり　型に　はまれば すごい威力を発揮する。
Goran, give me an update. Goran, do you read me?
クイズを出そう。 ん？
Goran! Could they have already taken him out?
「何でも切れる刀」 具現化できるか　否か。
Anyone from Goran's squad out there?
できない。 理由は？
Give me a report!
人間の能力の限界を 超えているから。
Hey... We can't see anything with all this smoke...
その通りだ。
We've been trying to reach Squadron
Leader Goran, but he won't respond!
具現化能力を １００％極めたとしても
I've lost contact with him!
具現化できないものは　ある。 「とても丈夫で よく切れる刀」なら　具現化　可能。
He was right beside me a moment ago! He just vanished into the smoke!
だが　それなら 実際の名刀を買ったほうがいい。
With all these messages,
I can't tell what's happening...
修行の必要もないしな。
They should've established a communication
network to operate in the leader's absence.
まぁ　消したり出したりは 「念」と違って　できないが
Baital squad, forward! Find Goran's squadron and converge with them.
実在するものを　ただ具現化しても 有効な武器にはならないが かといって　あまりに 神懸かったものは具現化できない。
Zemu and Pokoro squadrons will act
as rearguard for the Baital squad!
何を具現化するかは 慎重に考えて探すことだ。
Proceed in a V formation!
すさまじい集中力　イメージ力 多くの修行が不可欠だからな。 驚きだわ。 ん？
The number of soldiers is dropping.
わずか半年ほどで 「念」を習得して来るなんて…。
What's happening?
で　どんな雇い主が　お望み？
Now.
((「クモ」について いいことを教えよう))
Hey, Baital?
ヨークシンで行われるオークションに 強い権力を持つ人物がいい。 仕事の内容は問わない。
So you're next?
強い権力を持つ依頼人は 当然　要求も厳しいわよ。 ハンター歴ゼロ年のあんたを 雇うとは思えないけど…。
Are you sure this is a good idea? What do you mean? All we do is send enemies to the old man.
あっ　３人いるわ。
He's the one who takes them out.
あんたの条件で 「経験問わず　面接で判断」っての。
This is a little too easy.
３人とも身辺警護込みの依頼よ。
But it is a surefire method. Can't argue there.
内容を読むから選んで。
The Chairman was being modest...
１人目　拳銃マニア。
He's still much stronger than we are.
「特に　ミゼット社の『ゴルスネーク５５』 限定生産数の　ナンバー００１　求む」。
And he seems rather excited about this.
２人目　骨董皿収集家。
Oh, speak of the devil.
「ロド社製　記念皿 １６５５年と１６５７年もの」。
Keep sending them my way. I'm finally starting to regain my touch.
３人目　人体収集家。
Impressive...
「全身入れ墨皮の昇龍図　極美品。
And how about the Queen?
ゼリー症の幼児頭部　エトセトラ」。
She hasn't made a move. The Queen is still holed up in her nest.
いい趣味してるわ さて　誰にする？ ん？
Then the King hasn't been born yet.
鎖？ ああ　具現化系と聞いた時 最初に頭に浮かんだものだ。
Continue to monitor the situation. Roger that.
鎖ねぇ…　何でだろうな。
The old man's on a roll.
地獄に　つないでおかねば ならないような連中が
Shall we grab another squadron? Yeah.
そうかねぇ… 俺には縛られてるのは　むしろ
Baital and Gafutsu's squadrons haven't returned.
お前自身のような気がするがね。
We're down to fourteen squadrons.
貴様に何が分かる。
Damned humans.
てめぇ！　ちょっと待て！ 一応　俺は師匠だぞ！
How are they managing to whittle us down?
話も途中だ！　待て　こら！ さっきも言っただろ。 ただの鎖を物質化しても 意味ねえんだぞ！
I don't know. All I know is that there are some
humans who are very strong.
かといって 絶対に　ちぎれない鎖なんて
We know too little about humans.
具現化不可能だ！
They appear to possess a variety
of powers far stronger than ours.
９月１日　ヨークシンで行われる 世界最大のオークション
However, once the King is born,
we will hold the advantage. Yes, I hope that will be the case.
何て心音なの… すさまじい怒りの旋律
You want to come out? Not yet.
ヨークシンのオークションに コネのある人物を
Okay, that's three hours! Oh? Already?
紹介してほしいっつうわけね。
That seemed fast.
ええ。
Then I'll give you a thirty-minute break.
さっきのコと同じね。 えっ？
Huh? Aren't we supposed to fight Knuckle now?
今日は　同じ依頼が２件 面白いわ。
You can go once you're rested.
さっきのコ…？
Defeat him.
知ってんの？ えっ…　いいえ。
You have a little over a day
before the Chairman's deadline.
彼もオークションに…
This may be your first and last chance.
あの　すさまじい怒りの心音は 一体…
Well, if they're able to fight at full strength,
they'll have to accept the results, win or lose.
ひいっ！ こんなチンケな野郎と メシ食っても　まずいだけだろ。
Now, the problem is figuring out my escape...
ブサイクな男のガードは ノーサンキュー。 ナメるもの大概にしろよ！
Seems you kids are serious tonight.
分かってるよ　エリザ 今度の仕事が　うまく行けば…。
Youpi?
ああ　大丈夫だって お前１人ぐらい…
To be precise, your name is Menthuthuyoupi.
いや　もちろん　犬達も一緒に 全部　俺が面倒を見る。 心配するな　エリザ もう少しの辛抱だ。
I'm hungry.
ああ　問題ない。 とにかく　俺に任せとけ。
Before we begin, I want to
know where your partner is.
『千耳会』から紹介されて来た クラピカという者だ。
That's a riot! If you defeat me, I'll tell you. We might not get a chance to ask you then.
お待たせしました。
After another four or five warm-up punches, I'll get serious...
お揃いになりましたので
Better watch yourself.
ただ今より 契約に関する説明を行います。
I warm up fast.
[TV] 早速だが　条件を伝える。
Still no one coming out today? No.
[TV]　君らがライセンスを 持っているか否かは問わない。
As expected, they've holed up inside.
[TV]　要は　こちらが望むものを 手に入れてくれるかどうかだ。
Shall we make our move?
[TV]　オークションの開催まで あと１か月あるが
No, we're approaching the
deadline for your disciples.
それまでに　これから渡す リストの中から１つ どれでもいいから探して来てくれ。 どうぞ データカードでございます。
We can wait until that's over. Judging by the estimated number of
bodies currently stored in the nest, they'll need to replenish in a week or so. I would like to dispatch another
あっ…。 あ？　どうした　顔色が悪いぜ。
We can't count on them for anything in a fight. At best, they could act as decoys.
あぁ　クルタ族の眼球な！
Hell, they'd probably get in our way...
「入手難度Ａ。
I'm certain of it.
死後　緋色で定着したもの 頭部とセットがベスト」。
That old man always was a gambler...
聞いたことあるぜ！ クルタ族ってのは 興奮状態になると目が緋色…。
Want to bet whose disciples
will show up tomorrow?
黙れ。
I'll put 100,000 Jenny on Knuckle and Shoot.
黙ってろ。
If we're both wrong,
the Chairman gets the money.
くっ！
How about it?
[TV]　もう一度　言う　探し出すのは
Sure.
そのリストの中の１つだけでいい。
Then, I'll put...
[TV]　それをクリアすれば
...1,000,000 on them.
正式に契約し 護衛と収集活動を担ってもらう。
Huh? That's just impossible!
[TV]　では　健闘を祈る。
Are you trying to throw your money to the dogs? The Chairman is a dog?
必ず探し出す
I happen to love gambling.
まずは取り入る 信頼を得るために 画面越しに話していた人物は 恐らく　依頼主ですらない
I always roll high...
この距離を 限りなくゼロにする
There!
相手が気を許し　秘密の共有をも 求めて来るほどに
Behind you, fool!
人体収集家同士の 横のつながりがあるはずだ
He's still warming up?
ヘドの出る欲望を比べ合う ゲスどもの交友録
Damn, he's strong! But why is Knuckle... Could it be...
必ず手に入れて 一網打尽にしてやる
Hey, aren't you going to use
that "First comes rock" thing?
ん？　開かねえぜ？
Well, you won't be able to use that technique.
[TV]　１つ　言い忘れたが
It's flawed, after all.
強いことが雇用の最低条件だ。
It's flawed? A word of advice...
[TV]　その館から 無事　出られるくらい 最低な！
If you try that technique,
I'll stop you in your tracks.
あっ…。
Your technique has two huge weaknesses!
今　彼の 新たな戦いの幕が開く
I'm not sure I can accomplish this mission